[{"answer": " my friend, meet Senor my friend, subject of an al", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " I came all the way down here same as you did.  Keep from gettin' killed. Happened to see those jarheads beatin' on a good colla", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Whatta we do about the Mex", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You'll take him", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You'll take him", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "He's all yours. And I'm not your partner", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I always won. You a fight fan", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Blood on the premises", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The lab'll be the judge of that", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm bored", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm gonna take those two guys outside. Maybe they knew the cooz", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "...my friend had this gift, you see. She was so sweet and eager to please...a bit dumb, maybe. But she'd do anything to be liked, become whatever you wanted her to be. She'd walk like you, or talk like you...but she wasn't...she was still her", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Sure. She had this viewfinder and showed it around to all the guys. Said it was from the director. A c", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Did she ever tell you she was in a movie? Sometime around November", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Did she say what it was", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Your name please", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Relax, my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You're cute", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "That's all anyone ever wants to voluntee", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You don't have to tell me thi", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I like you, too", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Last summer I was ba", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes. That's all of it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Serve my family right", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No. I don't", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Where was that", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Why would you do that", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'll pick you up in fort", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I have an apartment, you know", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Tell me about the my friend's missing days you whoremonger! Tell me", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Tell me what you know", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Black-Dahlia_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Those girls and that family. How do you know them", "qsentId": 34}]